<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tel Aviv Guide</string>
    <string name="category_main">Tel Aviv</string>
    <string name="category_restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="category_markets">Markets</string>
    <string name="category_Museums">Museums</string>
    <string name="category_other_attractions">Other Attractions</string>
    <string name="main_screen_title">About the city</string>
    <string name="main_screen_text">Tel Aviv is one of the most vibrant cities in the world.
        Titled the ‘Mediterranean Capital of Cool’ by the New York Times, this is a 24 hour city with a unique pulse,
        combining sandy Mediterranean beaches with a world-class nightlife, a buzzing cultural scene, incredible food,
        UNESCO recognized architecture, and an international outlook. </string>

    <!--Restaurants fragment strings-->
    <string name="restaurant1">Manta Ray</string>
    <string name="restaurant1_description">Located along side the sands of the beach, and just steps away from the clashing waves,
    its kitchen is unique for its special and creative Middle Eastern cuisine. </string>
    <string name="restaurant1_address">703 Yehezkel Kaufman St. Tel Aviv</string>
    <string name="restaurant1_phone">+972 (0)3 5174773</string>
    <string name="restaurant1_link">http://mantaray.co.il/index.php/manta-ray-en</string>
    <string name="restaurant2">Nanuchka</string>
    <string name="restaurant2_description">The first 100% vegan Georgian restaurant in Tel Aviv and in the World!
        Besides the profusion of flavors and colors, here you will find antique flooring, tables with character,
        authentic tableware and warm lighting fixtures that make you feel right at home.
        On the walls you will find pieces of art, made by some of the best Israeli artists.
        All of these together create an intriguing and vibrant energy, which will leave you with a taste for more.</string>
    <string name="restaurant2_address">Lilienblum 30 Tel Aviv</string>
    <string name="restaurant2_phone">+972 (0)3 5162254</string>
    <string name="restaurant2_link">http://nanuchka.co.il/en/</string>
    <string name="restaurant3">Doctor Shakshuka</string>
    <string name="restaurant3_description">Dr. Shakshuka is a legendary and popular Tel Aviv budget-friendly family-run
        restaurant that serves simple yet delicious Tripolitan food. The restaurant hides in the small alleys
        near the famous Jaffa Flea Market.</string>
    <string name="restaurant3_address">Beit Eshel 3 Yaffa, Tel Aviv</string>
    <string name="restaurant3_phone">+972 (0)3 6913088</string>
    <string name="restaurant3_link">http://www.doctorshakshuka.co.il/#</string>
    <string name="restaurant4">Taizu</string>
    <string name="restaurant4_description">With a kitchen that is based on local street food from five
        Southeast Asian countries: India, China, Thailand, Vietnam and Cambodia,
        Taizu manages to pull off sophisticated Pan-Asian food with Mediterranean touches.</string>
    <string name="restaurant4_address">Menachem Begin 23 Tel Aviv</string>
    <string name="restaurant4_phone">+972 (0)3 5225005</string>
    <string name="restaurant4_link">https://www.taizu.co.il/en/</string>
    <string name="restaurant5">Kitchen Market</string>
    <string name="restaurant5_description">Kitchen Market is a contemporary gourmet restaurant on the upper floor
        of Shuk HaNamal market in the Tel Aviv port. One side offers an unending view of the sparkling sea,
        and another looks out over the vibrant color of the bustling marketplace. This,
        combine with fresh quality ingredients, and the bright, beautifully design of the restaurant,
        guarantee a first-class culinary experience.</string>
    <string name="restaurant5_address">Hangar 12, Tel-Aviv Port, Farmers Market 2nd floor, Tel Aviv</string>
    <string name="restaurant5_phone">+972 (0)3 5446669</string>
    <string name="restaurant5_link">http://www.kitchen-market.co.il/</string>
    <string name="restaurant6">Dallal - the restaurant</string>
    <string name="restaurant6_description">Dallal is located in the historic neighborhood of Neve Tzedek.
        Dallal offers a classic European kitchen with Mediterranean influences, using top notch seasonal ingredients.</string>
    <string name="restaurant6_address">Shabazi 10 Tel Aviv</string>
    <string name="restaurant6_phone">+972 (0)3 5109292</string>
    <string name="restaurant6_link">http://dallal.co.il/?lang=en</string>

    <!--Markets fragment strings-->
    <string name="market1">Carmel Market</string>
    <string name="market1_description">The Market is among the most central and popular of Tel Aviv’s market places
        - it’s also an integral part of the city’s early urban development. Thanks to a recent renovation,
        the Carmel Shuk of today is home to a range culinary treats that,together with covered walkways and shaded coffee stalls,
        welcomes leading chefs from Israel and abroad to its abundant sights, sounds and flavors.</string>
    <string name="market1_address">Span from the central HaCarmel Street through to the Kerem HaTeimanim neighborhood</string>
    <string name="market1_link">http://en.shuktlv.co.il/category/carmel-market</string>
    <string name="market2">Levinsky Market</string>
    <string name="market2_description">The market started has a range of spice shops and eateries opened up across the
        neighborhood in the 1930s, by the residents that came mostly from Saloniki, Greece.
        Today, among the stores to visit are dried fruits and nuts, bakeries, delicatessens and restaurants.</string>
    <string name="market2_address">Spreads across Levinsky Street, between HaAliyah Street and Herzl Street</string>
    <string name="market2_link">http://en.shuktlv.co.il/category/levinsky-market</string>
    <string name="market3">Shuk HaNamal</string>
    <string name="market3_description">Inspired by covered food markets in Europe, the Namal Shuk takes its food cues
        from the slow food movement. The Namal Shuk is teaming with ripe, fresh, local produce and products ranging
        from sea foods to jams and cured meats to coffees. It is open from Monday through Saturday (closed Sundays) and
        on Fridays a colorful farmer’s market takes over the parking lot next door. </string>
    <string name="market3_address">Hanger 12 at Tel Aviv Port boardwalk</string>
    <string name="market3_link">http://en.shuktlv.co.il/category/shuk-hanamal</string>
    <string name="market4">Jaffa Flea Market - Shuk HaPishpushim</string>
    <string name="market4_description">Like many other major cities across Europe and North America, Jaffa’s Shuk HaPishpushim,
        or Flea Market, is an outdoor secondhand and antique shopping extravaganza.
        In recent years it became a trendy spot for fashionistas, artisans and lovers of all things old or handmade.
        Today’s sprawling streets and central market area are an eclectic mix of indoor restaurants, stop by eateries,
        outdoor junk vendors, and shops with refurbished furniture, household items from earlier periods,
        and second hand clothes.</string>
    <string name="market4_address">Runs across the streets of Olei Zion, Yehuda Margoza, Beit Eshel and the alleyways connecting them</string>
    <string name="market4_link">http://en.shuktlv.co.il/category/jaffa-flea-market</string>

    <!--Museums fragment strings-->
    <string name="museum1">Tel Aviv Museum of Art</string>
    <string name="museum1_description">One of Israel leading artistic and cultural institutions. It comprises various departments:
        The Department of Israeli Art, the Department of Modern and Contemporary Art, the Department of Prints and Drawings,
        the Department of Photography, the Department of Architecture and Design, and the Old Masters Department.
        In addition to its extensive program of permanent and changing exhibitions, the museum offers a vibrant selection of
        programs and activities for adults, youth and children: concerts, classes, lectures, guided tours, workshops, and more.
        The museum is currently situated in three main buildings: The Helena Rubinstein Pavilion for Contemporary Art that was
        in 1959 and today showcases mainly temporary exhibitions, the Main Building on Shaul Hamelech Boulevard which opened
        in 1971, and adjacent to it the new Herta and Paul Amir Building that was inaugurated in the Fall of 2011 and was
        designed by American architect Preston Scott Cohen. The museum's extended exhibition space also includes the Lola
        Beer Ebner Sculpture Garden, Nata's Garden, and the Joseph and Rebecca Meyerhoff Art Education Center.</string>
    <string name="museum1_phone">+972 (0)3 6077020</string>
    <string name="museum1_address">Shaul Hamelech Blvd. 27, The Golda Meir Cultural and Art Center, Tel Aviv</string>
    <string name="museum1_link">http://www.tamuseum.org.il/tel-aviv-museum-of-art</string>
    <string name="museum2">Eretz Israel Museum</string>
    <string name="museum2_description">This is a multidisciplinary museum that focuses on the history and culture of Israel
        through comprehensive permanent and temporary exhibits in the diverse fields of archeology, ethnography,
        post and philately, folklore, Judaica, traditional crafts, popular art, cultural history and local identity.
        The museum spread over an area of some 20 acres and comprises about 15 buildings and various installations.
        In the center of the museum, adjacent to the buildings and exhibit spaces, stands Tell Qasile -
        an ancient archaeological mound dating from the 12th century BCE. Additional ancient relics, such as mosaics,
        oil presses, an ancient wine press, flour mills, etc. can be found in the gardens surrounding the site.
        In addition to the ten permanent exhibitions and ancient sites, the museum displays about 20 temporary exhibits
        every year and also conducts symposiums, lectures and meetings with curators and scholars in various fields.
        The museum site also houses an innovative planetarium, halls of various sizes, lecture rooms and workshops,
        a cafeteria, and a gift shop.</string>
    <string name="museum2_phone">+972 (0)3 6415244</string>
    <string name="museum2_address">Haim Levanon 2 Ramat Aviv, Tel Aviv </string>
    <string name="museum2_link">http://www.eretzmuseum.org.il/e/90/</string>
    <string name="museum3">Nahum Gutman Museum of Art</string>
    <string name="museum3_description">The Museum opened in 1988 by the Nahum Gutman Society and the Tel Aviv Foundation.
        The entire collection was donated by the Gutman family. The museum was established in a historical house,
        built in 1887, known as "The Writers' House". Through the years the house was badly damaged and was finally abandoned
        in the 1960s. It was declared a landmark and subsequently purchased by the Jewish National Fund. Reconstruction began
        in 1992 and the northern wing was historically reconstructed, while the southern wing was modernly renovated by the
        architect Ronny Zeibert. In 2009 the new adjacent wing of the museum was officially opened, where the "Nukata",
        the Turkish Guard had once stood, during the founding of Neve-Zedek.
        The museum exhibitions create a meeting space between Gutman and young Israeli contemporary artists, creating a cultural
        dialogue between old and new works of art. The fact that Gutman drew both Tel Aviv and Jaffa, portraying Jews and Arabs
        with the same amount of love and interest, provides us with a wonderful tool for the teaching of tolerance as well as
        a cross-cultural meeting place. </string>
    <string name="museum3_phone">+972 (0)3 5161970</string>
    <string name="museum3_address">Shimon Rokah 21 Tel Aviv</string>
    <string name="museum3_link">http://www.gutmanmuseum.co.il/en/the-museum/about-us</string>
    <string name="museum4">Rubin Museum</string>
    <string name="museum4_description">The Museum is an artist-house-museum in the historical heart of Tel Aviv. Formerly the
        home of the painter Reuven Rubin that lived here with his family and worked in his third floor studio from 1946 until
        his death in 1974. Constructed in 1930, the house was opened to the public in 1983. A selection from the permanent
        collection of the artist paintings is regularly on display, replaced periodically by guest exhibitions focusing on
        Israeli art. There are 4 floors in the building: The street level floor houses the main gallery, as well as the entry
        hall with the museum's shop. An additional gallery is located on the second floor, with a library and reading room.
        The children's workshop is located in the basement, opening to the backyard. Rubin's studio, preserved as it was in
        his lifetime, is located on the third floor which also houses a biographical photographic display unfolding Rubin's
        life-story and reflecting the local artistic and cultural scene.</string>
    <string name="museum4_phone">+972 (0)3 5255961</string>
    <string name="museum4_address">Bialik 14 Tel Aviv</string>
    <string name="museum4_link">http://www.rubinmuseum.org.il/en/company/about/main/</string>

    <!--OtherAttractions fragment strings-->
    <string name="others1">Jaffa Port</string>
    <string name="others1_description">One of the oldest ports in the world, in operation since the Canaanite period,
        the Jaffa Port bestows on Jaffa a historical status as a major city in the Eastern Mediterranean and a Western
        gateway to Israel. For thousands of years, the port has served fishermen, ships, merchants, pilgrims, conquerors
        and immigrants. Over time, the Jaffa Port has suffered periods of neglect and abandonment. Thanks to a joint effort
        by port fishermen, local residents and admirers, and Tel-Aviv/Jaffa Municipality investment and support, the port
        doubles as a fishing port but also as an attraction that offers an array of cultural, recreational, commercial and
        tourist activities to the general public. </string>
    <string name="others1_phone">+972 (0)3 6832255</string>
    <string name="others1_address">Nemal Yafo St. Jaffa-Tel-Aviv</string>
    <string name="others1_link">https://www.namalyafo.co.il/en/about/</string>
    <string name="others2">Beaches</string>
    <string name="others2_description">Tel Aviv-Yafo boasts a long promenade, running alongside the seashore that makes up
        its western edge. People walk, jog, ride bikes, or sit on benches and fill their lungs with fresh air, all while
        being surrounded by a glorious 8.7 mile stretch of open views, blue horizons, and white sails bobbing on the waves.
        Each of the 13 beautiful beaches enjoys unique characteristics and offers a variety of services, including lifeguard
        stations, kiosks, restaurants, children’s playgrounds, outdoors gyms, and more.</string>
    <string name="others2_address">The Seashore - the West side of Tel Aviv</string>
    <string name="others2_link">https://www.go-telaviv.com/tel-aviv-beach.html</string>
    <string name="others3">White City of Tel-Aviv</string>
    <string name="others3_description">In 2003 UNESCO proclaimed the historic zone of Tel Aviv, also know as The White City,
        as a World Cultural Heritage site. By this proclamation, UNESCO recognized the special architectural qualities of
        the buildings, streets, squares and avenues of this zone. The White City area was built in an innovative style,
        tailored to the needs of its residents, to their life styles, and to the climatic conditions of the region. This
        area is the world's largest grouping of buildings designed in the International Style known as Bauhaus.</string>
    <string name="others3_address">Between Ben-Gurion st. in the north, Chen Blvd in the East and Neve Tzedek
        neighborhood in Tel Aviv</string>
    <string name="others3_link">https://www.tel-aviv.gov.il/en/Visit/WhiteCity/Pages/default.aspx</string>
    <string name="others4">Tel Aviv Port</string>
    <string name="others4_description"> In 2001, the management of Marine Trust Ltd., in collaboration with the Municipality
        of Tel Aviv, decided to restore the first Hebrew port to the first Hebrew city. The port, which since the 1960s had
        been a backyard that was cut off from the city, became, after the environmentally friendly reconstruction, and
        renovation of the original buildings, into a unique meeting point between the city, residents and the sea, and one
        of the most beautiful and lively leisure and entertainment venues in Tel Aviv–Jaffa.</string>
    <string name="others4_address">North Entrance - at the junction between Hataarucha Street and the end of Dizengoff St.,
        Tel Aviv</string>
    <string name="others4_link">http://www.yarid-hamizrach.co.il/</string>
    <string name="others5">Hayarkon Park</string>
    <string name="others5_description"> The Park is set on the outskirts of Tel Aviv. the beautifully tranquil Park
        is the green lung of Tel Aviv and straddles the Yarkon River in the north of the city. Aside from the sheer
        beauty and tranquility of the neatly groomed lawns abutting the calm river, the Park also has some interesting
        features. In the eastern part lie the Rock Garden and the Tropical Garden. There is a five-acre Tropical Garden
        which is home to a rain forest-like micro-climate with a tiny lake home to swans, fish, and beautiful orchids and vines.
        Also within the Park is one of Israel’s largest water parks (complete with water slides, a wave pool and a toddlers’
        pool) and an outdoor stadium for concerts and performances.</string>
    <string name="others5_address">Near the Yarkon river in Tel Aviv</string>
    <string name="others5_link">http://park.co.il/en/</string>
    <string name="link_text_shown">Click here for more information</string>
</resources>
